EKATERINA GLOAGUEN

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



+33 7 66 23 90 50



ek.gloaguen.vasileva@icloud.com



29200 Brest, France





PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

LARAVEL 9. 2023

SYMFONY 6 Udemy, 2022

PHP7 Udemy, 2022

WEB DEVELOPMENT Udemy, 2022

PYTHON Coursera, 2021

SKILLS

- PHP
- JavaScript
- Symfony 6
- mySQL
- Laravel 8, 9,10
- Git
- Bootstrap
- Pvthon
- Tailwind CSS
- Statistica
- HTML
- WordPress
- iQuery

LANGUAGES

English: C1 French: C1 Italian: A2

Russian: Native

EDUCATION

MASTER MARINE BIOLOGY

The University of Naples Federico II 2021

MASTER of PSYCHOLOGY

Saint Petersburg State University 2017

BACHELOR of BIOLOGY

Saint Petersburg State University 2015

PROFILE

As a passionate web developer with over 3 years of experience in the IT industry, including 2+ years of IT recruiting, and a strong scientific background in Biology and Cognitive Psychology, I bring a unique blend of skills to the table. With top-notch communication abilities, a commitment to continuous learning, and a drive for excellence, creativity, and innovation, I am a highly skilled and dependable developer. I offer a fresh perspective and deep understanding of the field, making me a valuable asset to any team. Let's connect and discuss how we can collaborate to achieve your goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PHP WEB DEVELOPER December 2022-current Data Sfera Development of the back-end of different web applications (cms) using:

PHP8+

Laravel 8

MySQL

Git

JavaScript jQuery

HTML CSS

IT RECRUITER (travel tech) 2018 - 2020 Sputnik8

The company has grown 2.5 times, with more than 30 new recruits

Search and assessment of potential candidates, tech and soft skills interview, junior developers and QA engineers tutoring

MASTER PSYCHOLOGY THESIS PROJECT 2016 - 2017 SPBU

Scientific research, Academic writing, research project using Python, Data analysis using Statistica & R

ASSISTANT WEBMASTER 2015 - 2016 FX-PR.com

Realization of new sales support tools WordPress